

## Seattle, WA 98125 | (414) - 429 - 0564 | mark.heil1122@gmail.com

# **Professional Summary**

After 15 years in the printing industry I am looking for new opportunities. I am excited to learn new things while applying the experience I already have. I am also currently a student in a full stack web development bootcamp course.

# Skills

- Process improvement
- Web development projects
- Agile workflow processes
- Layout development
- Web development

- Image manipulation
- Website graphics
- Adobe Creative Suite
- MS Office
- HTML / CSS / JavaScript

# Work History

Deli Clerk / Cook 04/2018 to Current

Fred Meyer – Seattle, WA

- Improved teamwork and leadership skills with Deli Associates.
- Handled busy, fast-paced situations and agitated customers with relative ease while remaining professional and calm.

# **Offset Printing Press Operator**

07/2016 to 03/2020

BCT Seattle - Seattle, WA

- Managed Offset printing operations and improved production efficiency.
- Established good communincation between departments for better production.

#### **Napkin Print Press Operator**

07/2005 to 06/2016

Creative Converting – Clintonville, WI

- Adjusted press during production runs to maintain specific registration and color densities.
- Examined job orders to determine quantity, stock specifications, colors and special printing instructions.

### Education

Associate Degree: Printing and Publishing

WAUKESHA COUNTRY TECHNICAL COLLEGE - Pewaukee, WI